1. Do you agree that celebrities start fashion trends? Why or why not? Give examples.

	A : I agree. Because the fashion of celebrities who appear in drama or movie are often sold out.

2. There’s an old saying: “Clothes make the man” (or woman). What do you think this saying means? Do you agree? Why or why not?

	A : I don't agree. Because if a general person wears strange dress. It's so strange. But if Wonbin does, that's not strange. As a result, the fashion doesn't make man, but the man does.

3. Is choosing the clothes you wear a creative activity? Why or why not?

	A : Choosing the clothes is creative. Because it reflects in personality of individual.

4. What are some ways people use color as camouflage or as a sign of danger?

	A : Soldiers use camouflage cream in army. And people use signs of black and yellow in danger traffic area.

5. Most large predators, like lions, are not brightly colored. Why do you think this is true?

	A : Both prey and predator are not brightly colored. But the reasons are different. Preys are not brightly colored to protect themselves. However, Predators are not brightly colored to catch the preys before detected.

6. Which house do you prefer—the Great Bamboo Wall House or Hundertwasser House? Why?

	A : I prefer Great Bamboo Wall House by Kuma Kengo. Because it made natural material like wood, bamboo, earth and even paper.

7. Think of a time when someone was rude to you. What did you do and say?

	A : I was a little angry when someone was rude to me. But I relaxed in this situation.

8. How did you learn about manners or etiquette? Give examples.

	A : Mostly, I learn it from my parents. Sometimes I realized that it was a bad manner after I got a damage.

9. You are going to a formal dinner at someone’s home. Ask for advice about what to wear, what time to arrive, what to bring, what to talk about with guests, and table manners.

	A : First, the dressing should be comfortable for the opponent and I should arrive at the place before the dinner starts. Also we usually talk about the topic he is interested in. And if he is older than me, I won't start to eat earlier than him.

10. “Life is a game.” Do you agree with this statement? Why or why not?

	A : I agree. Because I can enjoy both game and life.

11. Games are fun to play. What are some other reasons to play games?

	A : The reason I play the games expect the fun is to kill the time and to develop relationship.

12. There is a well-known saying: “It’s not important whether you win or lose; it’s how you play the game.” What does this saying mean? How does it apply to games and to real life? Do you agree? Why or why not?

	A : I don't agree. Since result is more important than progress in some areas like going to the university, credit, getting a job etc...

1. Make a presentation on bad manners. Pick a topic, give examples of their bad manners, reasons, and what people should do.

	A : I think noise in library is a bad manner. Alarm of cellphone or clicking sound of mouse in library makes other people unpleasant. So the cellphone should be off and zippers on bags and pencil cases should be closed silently.

2. Tell me about your dream house. Explain in detail.

	A : My dream house is square. It's made of wood and its color is also wood. It has 2 floor and a big yard.

3. Do students at our school need to wear uniforms? Give reasons and examples.

	A : I think students need to wear uniforms. Because first they can feel a sense of belonging. Also as benefit of uniform shop increases, economy is activated.